everything he catches against Mr. Doctor he's going to
todo lo que pille contra Mr doctor va a
try to expose him and you'll suck his tail
intentar exponerlo y tú comerle el rabo
pet all of that's why it's better not to see
mascota todo por eso es mejor no ver
but Ah that's why it's better not to see this
pero Ah por eso es mejor no ver este no
isn't the one who says clearly Don't go so he
es el que dice claro No vayase que te
sees you and we find out who you are no Ah that's why it's
vea y nos enteremos de quién eres no Ah
better not to see Do you remember
por eso es mejor no ver Te acuerdas
when he said it's not that Javi doesn't want them to
cuando decía él no es que Javi no quiere
see us because they'll know the
que nos vean porque van a saber la
truth if they see us it's that he was a climber you're
verdad si nos ven es que era un trepa
a climber that you've been there
eres un trepa que has estado ahí
exposing Delox and as soon as
exponiendo a delox y a la mínima que
Delox told you eun I'm not a scammer anymore I'm
delox te dijo eun ya no soy un estafador
going to give you an interview and you're going
te voy a dar una entrevista y ya me vas
to defend me from today on you
a defender a partir de hoy fuiste
ran to pay 50 for the
corriendo a pagar 50 del programa de las
interview program because it was the dream of your
entrevistas porque era el sueño de tu
life finally you believed that you were going to have
vida por fin te creías que ibas a tener
5,000 viewers there that's why it
ahí 5,000 espectadores por eso también
's also good that you know who he is in case you know which one
es bueno que sepáis quién es para si os